=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 26=
= الحلقة 26 =
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
You're so ugly!
أنت قبيح جدا!
Ugly?
البشع؟
You have no taste.
ليس لديك ذوق.
I was just cross-dressing.
كنت فقط أرتدي ملابس.
Your taste is horrible.
ذوقك فظيع.
Sir.
سيد.
Everything is under control. Please show up.
كل شيء تحت السيطرة.  يرجى الحضور.
Sir, while she's sleeping,
سيدي ، بينما هي نائمة ،
cast a spell and possess her.
يلقي تعويذة وامتلاكها.
She was frightened... by you.
كانت خائفة ... منك.
How did you find out?
كيف عرفت؟
I'm great, right?
أنا بخير ، صحيح؟
You're too ugly.
أنت قبيح جدا.
Turn... around.
التف حوله.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
You're too ugly.
أنت قبيح جدا.
You're breaking my heart.
أنت تحطم قلبي.
I've followed you for so many years.
لقد تابعتك لسنوات عديدة.
Even you dislike me? I shall leave.
حتى أنت لا تحبني؟  سأرحل.
This isn't expected.
هذا غير متوقع.
My possession spell worked.
عملت تعويذة الحيازة.
Sir.
سيد.
You just turned into a woman.
لقد تحولت للتو إلى امرأة.
Look at how happy you are.
انظر إلى مدى سعادتك.
Stupid.
غبي.
Am I happy
هل انا سعيد
because I became a woman?
لأني أصبحت امرأة؟
Why else then?
وإلا فلماذا إذن؟
It's because
انه بسبب
it feels so great
إنه شعور رائع جدًا
to not stammer.
حتى لا تتلعثم.
Wuyou, you're finally awake.
وويو ، لقد استيقظت أخيرًا.
Share with me
شاركني
the experience of forming a family.
تجربة تكوين الأسرة.
(Bright Future)
(مستقبل مشرق)
Young Master.
(مستقبل مشرق) السيد الشاب.
Could you have...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
What? What happened?
ماذا؟  ماذا حدث؟
Am I dreaming?
هل أنا في حلم؟
Honey, why did you pinch me?
عزيزتي ، لماذا قرصتني؟
I'm not dreaming.
أنا لا أحلم.
The ancestor of Rong Family.
جد عائلة رونغ.
I did not let you down.
أنا لم أخذلك.
Why are you being so noisy early in the morning?
لماذا تكون صاخبًا جدًا في الصباح الباكر؟
Chuchu.
حلمات.
No. Madam.
رقم سيدتي.
The forbidden skill on Young Master is neutralized.
يتم تحييد المهارة المحظورة على السيد الصغير.
He's now worthy of the name of
إنه الآن يستحق اسم
Demon Emperor.
شيطان الإمبراطور.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪